Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure!
What the?
Why am I a kid?
Tommy!
Little boy, are you all right there?
I'll clean those wounds up
and put some medicine on you.
That's impossible!
Chariot, help!
Yes! Yes!
I'm not strong enough
to beat him like this.
I don't see that nice lady anywhere.
Where'd she go?
She couldn't have just vanished.
She was sitting right behind me.
I didn't even hear a scream.
What'd he do to her?
Where could she have gone?
I'll pull the wrap.
As I recall, you said the
shampoo stings your eyes.
And since it looks like
you've got some in there.
Allow me to help you wash it out!
Now this won't take long.
You and me.
I will see you.
Keep your truth.
You still watch me.
Not again.
You still
watch me.
I have begun for the diamonds.
But you know
how the word is.
I have been given by all brothers.
Me Suzi Boss to a ma da mi ne sadame.
Ji ta Dead Kill, kei sen no Diego.
Utsu beki Dario o no wab.
Stop it now!
Hajima te shima ta monogatari ni.
Uba wa Radio ma ma no Diego ni.
of the
C 'est mauvais, having bite-sized arms
is going to wind up getting me killed!
If only these stupid arms of
mine were just a little longer,
I'd be able to poke his eyes
out and make a run for it!
So, even in the face of death,
you've got to pull the plug.
However...
With your hair clogging, in the water's
only exit, it'll take even longer!
for the tub to completely drain.
I'd say you'll have five,
maybe 10 minutes left.
You may as well throw in the towel now.
You're going down for a permanent nap.
Good night!
Horrid dreams, you little brat!
I'll die!
How does it feel knowing that
you're utterly helpless, vulnerable?
What the hell is that thing?
It can't be, but from the shape
and color, it looks like...
There's no way.
No one in their right mind would think of
doing something so downright disgusting!
It's undeniable!
The smell proves it!
How foul!
You took a shit in the bathtub!
Guess I'm not so helpless after
all, you creepy four-eyed asshole!
How dare you do something like that?
Dear God!
Isn't there a shred of
human decency in your body?
What kind of hero would ever stoop
to doing something so disturbing?
You are a bad boy!
Very bad!
Shut up and tell me what
you did to that nice lady!
I want to know right now!
Where are you?
Where'd you go?
Lady, answer me!
Hey, lady!
Come on, you that stupid?
What do you think I did?
Whoa there!
It'd be wise for both of us to
watch where we step, Polnareff.
One wrong move and your lady friend is
likely to be squashed underfoot. Huh?
He... He wouldn't.
There's no way.
This can't be happening.
No!
It can't be!
Anyone who's unfortunate
enough to come into
contact with my stand
experiences time in reverse.
Luckily for you,
you saw me coming and jumped away
from my shadow at the last second,
buying yourself a few more years
than your friend down there.
But she had the misfortune of touching
my shadow for several seconds,
which is the reason she became a fetus!
She's alive for the time being,
but if I'm being honest with you,
she won't last long outside the
safety of her mother's womb.
That's what she gets!
She should have never tried to help
a pathetic piece of trash like you.
What a moron.
You are the worst kind
of person on this planet!
Crap, you gotta be kidding me. I just...
Oops, looks like you touched it again.
Which means you're going
to get even younger.
This time,
you'll probably regress to a diminutive
four-year-old version of yourself.
Not again!
This isn't good.
I have to hurry and beat this
guy, or the nice lady will.
At this rate, she only has a
matter of minutes before she dies.
I've got to find a way to defeat this
Alessi freak, and I've got to do it fast!
She took me in and fixed up all my wounds.
She was so caring.
I have to hurry.
There's absolutely no time to waste.
Get over here, will ya?
Where exactly do you think you're going?
You're not gonna get far
cradling a dying fetus.
Here's a fun idea.
Let's turn you into a fetus.
Damn it, not this again!
His dumb shadow keeps touching me!
Oh no, I'm getting even smaller!
Yahoo!
Oh boy!
There's no way in hell I'm gonna lose now!
Judging from your appearance, Polnareff,
you're what, three years old now?
Before you know it, your intellect will
be that of a three-year-old's as well.
Locking the door won't do
you any good, little one.
Made it! Huh?
Damn it, the stupid bars
are too close together!
Even a kid can't slip through!
But I have to find a way to get out of here
or that freak show's gonna kill us both!
Crap!
I can't cut them!
This is just too crude to be true.
I see that your chariot
has also become a toddler.
The bars are too tough
for its baby rapier.
I bet it's gotten slower too.
Ready or not, here I come!
Oh, Polnareff, here comes Alessi!
He's gone, huh?
Where did he go?
That brat!
It just vanished!
Or maybe the little
spunk monkey found a way
to slither through the bars in the window!
Clever, Bulnare, very clever.
You're trying to pull
a fast one, aren't you?
You think if you trick me into believing
you slipped through the window,
it'll distract me.
You must be hiding somewhere,
waiting to get the drop on me.
Not bad, runt.
Quite cunning indeed for
a miserable little shit.
Polnareff, come out, come
out, wherever you are.
You're so puny now, you could easily
be hiding in that drawer over there.
Yeah, he's probably hiding
in the bucket or the drawer.
Or maybe he's actually hiding
in that teddy bear by the wall.
Where could he be?
I've got a one in three chance!
And if at all possible, I'd
like to get him with one swing.
I'll crack open his infantile
skull with this axe!
I've decided you're tucking away
in that tattered old teddy bear!
But my second guess is...
This grandfathered clock, the
perfect hiding spot for a coward!
I guess I was wrong.
Then maybe he's...
Hiding in this rusty bucket!
But I...
So you are in the bear!
Then how about the drawer?
Where is he?
Where is he? Where is he?
He's gone! But how?
There's no way he could
have gotten out of here!
The walls, floor, and
ceiling are all stone.
Even if they were one centimeter
thick, Chariot couldn't break through.
And those bars are too narrow for him.
I saw it with my own eyes.
This is insane. Where is he?
Where did he go?
So, you were outsmarted by
a toddler, huh? What the?
Oh, man, Alessi.
What's going on here?
The goldfish just disappeared!
I was hiding in the fish tank the whole
time and used this mirror for camouflage!
A kid could've figured out my
plan and you totally fell for it!
I was worried that something
so simple wasn't gonna work,
but lucky for me, you're just
as stupid as you are creepy!
Doesn't matter if Cherry is
stuck in his two-year-old form,
he can still skewer your face, dumbass!
Ha ha ha!
Yaaaah!
Bad boy!
Bad boy! Hey!
Get your ass back here!
Honey! Hey, wait!
Until you break your stand
spell, I'm gonna keep attacking!
Bad boy! Bad boy!
You're such a bad boy!
Evolve, that...
that jerk dropped out the window!
Bad boy!
What a horrible boy!
Jotaro!
Crap!
If he's here, then I'm done for!
How'd he find us? Hmm.
Someone falling from a
window covered in blood.
You don't see that every day.
Stay calm.
At times like this, the winner
is the one who stays calm.
Just think about it, Alessi.
Jotaro must be looking for the
adult version of Polnareff.
He has no clue who I am.
I'll do what I always do.
Play dumb until the last minute.
Then attack him when he least expects it.
Oh, no!
My boss is going to be so very
angry with me when he finds out!
There I was, cleaning the window, and
I suddenly slipped and fell through!
What am I going to do?
I am in so much trouble!
Hold it right there, you
frizzy-haired freak show!
Hey, mister!
What was his name again?
Come on, what was it?
Now's my chance!
I was waiting for Polnareff to
poke his annoying little head out!
Getcha now, Jotaro!
Mister, watch out for his shadow!
I did it!
I really did it!
I managed to touch Jojuro's shadow!
Mr. No!
So, Jojuro, how does it feel to be
placed under the spell of my stand?
This feeling...
This is...
This is bad!
He's turning into a kid just like I did!
Oh, Jojuro!
I heard through the grapevine that you've
only recently developed your stand,
Star Platinum.
And that means you didn't have the ability
to use your stand when you were a kid.
So now you're nothing but ordinary.
Oh no, he's been turned into a little boy.
It looks like he can't be any
older than a seven-year-old.
Guess I'm the winner.
Hope you're watching, Master Dio,
because I'm about to kill Jojaro.
You'd better give me a good reward
for everything I've come through.
Now, Jujuru, it's time to die!
Oh, what a hit!
He decked him using only
his little kid fist!
Oh, good grief.
Don't underestimate me
just because I'm a kid.
Shut up!
What?
You're seriously telling me that Jocharo
could kick ass even as a little kid?
I knew he was tough, but he was
that strong as a kid? Bites!
You got off easy, friend,
but I can fix that.
Lannibal!
Stand, set,
God of Chaos and Storms,
Alessi, 38 years old,
single, and an unfortunate projectile,
out of commission!
Was all of that a dream?
This earring belongs to that boy.
So it really did happen.
I don't know why!
But for some reason!
I couldn't move my body.
That's right.
I may not have been able to move!
But I remember everything.
That sweet little boy.
Devoted himself to protecting me.
And risked his life.
By fighting against a grown man.
He had such a brave and heroic heart.
Oh, where did that boy go?
Where?
Where did my little knight run off to?
Where did you go?
Where are you?
I've never met such an
amazing woman before.
So kind. So genuine.
That was a close one, but thankfully
I'm back to my normal self.
I wonder if she's okay.
I hate to bother you,
but you didn't happen
to see a sweet little
boy leave my house in
something of a hurry,
did you?
He has silver hair.
Come to think of it, it
looks exactly like yours.
Pardon me for asking, but
have the two of us met before?
No, I didn't see a kid come through.
Sorry I couldn't help you.
Let's go, Jotaro.
Come on, hurry up!
Please wait!
Could you be...
That earring you're wearing...
The two of us have never met before.
It's not possible.
My friend and I are travelers.
So if you'll excuse us, there's
another town we need to get to.
We'll be going now.
It was only a dream.
Too bad.
Not a single word from you, Jotaro.
I don't want to hear it.
No!
Joe Dario and Polnareff!
Where in the world have
you two slackers been?
Ah, Mr.
Joestar and Avdol.
How many times have I told the two of
you not to go wandering off on your own?
Oh, you're in a position to talk.
You're the one who just disappeared.
Now, now.
Why don't we focus on getting
something to eat? Huh? Hey Iggy!
Where the hell have you been all day long?
Can I take that for you?
Yeah, thanks a million.
It's about time, we're finally
getting a bit of relief.
It was quite the late breakfast,
but I suppose it couldn't be helped.
Yeah, since we've almost made it to Cairo,
I think it's time we figured
out where Dio is hiding out.
oh we're doing this will it
appear I'm not sure but given that
we're so close the result should be
more precise all right here we go
excuse me sir is there a problem over
here everything's fine mind your own
Uh, yes.
Old man, tell us, what is it?
Just a little longer.
I see something.
It's getting clearer.
Take a good look!
There you have it, gentlemen!
Our final destination!
Thank you.
You're the one who fell for the scam.
I've had just about enough of your games.
Gambling is just like relationships.
The one who cries loses.
If he does anything that seems
suspicious, you can go home.
If you're scared, exactly right.
I'm going to bet my soul. Good?